[{"answer": "Seventeen thousand in debt.  Whew.  Is your e", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " There's more than one", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, please, it was long over by then.  God damn, he made me look like some cheap", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Bullshit.  You told me I'd get half a million dollars.  You told me I'd be set", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You want my number", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Which number do you want, my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Which number do you want, my friend", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Shit, yeah.  I got numbers coming out of my ears.  Like, for instance, ten", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Where've you been", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Don't use language with me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What kind of person lives like this?  Huh? What kind of person lets her kids run around in a house crawling with bugs the size of housecats", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "call an exterminator.  I can't afford one.  God, I can't even afford my .  I got fired", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Fax these to this number, okay", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "All of them", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "For your information, my friend cares what was in those ponds 'cause he used to spend half his day wading around them.  That was his job", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Really?  It makes me sick", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You didn't care about my case", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I can't.  Look", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I need it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Don't talk to me like I'm an idiot, okay?  I may not have a law degree, but I've spent 18 months on this case, and I know more about those plaintiffs than you ever will", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Whose number do you need", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "If you tell me to relax, I'm gonna kick your fucking head off", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "People don't fly down in their own god damn plane for", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Bullshit.  You'd drag me off my deathbed if it suited you", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend thought?  What about you?  Do you think anymore", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You're not gonna be there", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "This isn't doctor's orders.  It's mine.  I'm saying you can't come", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Because my friend doesn't want to work with you. He thinks you're a loose cannon", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I was working in the compressor, and out of nowhere the supervisor calls me up to the office and says, we're gonna give you a shredder machine, and send you on down to the warehouse.  We want you to get rid of all the documents stored out there", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Nope.  And I didn't ask", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't know what to say", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I was wrong", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "And he's making them give five million of it to you all", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Five million dollars", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yeah.  Yours is nicer", "docId": "Erin-Brockovich.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Here what comes", "qsentId": 38}]